<resources>
    <string name="app_name">DIUSS</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Daffodil International University</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">info@daffodilvarsity.edu.bd</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="player_error">Error: needed updated YouTube App or %s</string>
    <string name="supervisors_initial">Supervisors initial on this topic</string>

    <string name="to">To</string>
    <string name="subject">Subject</string>
    <string name="body">Body</string>
    <string name="profile_link">Profile Link</string>
    <string name="publication_project">Publication/Project</string>
    <string name="membership">Membership</string>
    <string name="training_experience">Training Experience</string>
    <string name="research_area">Research Area</string>
    <string name="department_of_cse">Department of CSE</string>
    <string name="my_shared_preference">my_shared_preference</string>
    <string name="show_case_preference_topic">show_case_preference_topic</string>
    <string name="show_case_preference_teacher">show_case_preference_teacher</string>
    <string name="selected_tab_position">selected tab position</string>

    <string name="home">Home</string>
    <string name="topics_and_supervisors">Topics and Supervisors</string>
    <string name="rules_and_regulations">Rules and Regulations</string>

    <string name="title_defense_registration_instructions">Title Defense Registration Instructions</string>
    <string name="details_title_defense_registration_instructions">Before starting your registration for Title Defense of current semester, check if you have all the necessary information. The required information for successful registration you will need:\n\n\u25CF Your team information (Team members ID, name, DIU email address, Phone Number)\n\u25CF Your tentative title\n\u25CF Your preferred choice (Development Project/ Research Project/ Internship)\n\u25CF Your preferred area of interest (In development projects: Android, iOS Mobile Application development, Web Solutions, JAVA Applications, Game Development etc. In research projects: Data Mining, Big Data, Could Computing, Human Computer Interaction, Natural Language Processing, Machine Learning, Internet of Things (IoT), Networking, Robotics, Bioinformatics, Software Engineering, Embedded Systems, Image Processing, Pattern Recognition etc.)\n\u25CF Your preferred choice of Supervisors. You can give choice of maximum three (3) supervisors. Make sure your area of interest matched with your supervisors area of interest. A list of supervisors for current is published.</string>

    <string name="title_defense_registration_process">Title Defense Registration Process</string>
    <string name="details_title_defense_registration_process">It is a 4 step registration process. <b>Only one member from each team should fill up this form. Multiple submission are strictly not encouraged.</b> \n\n<b>Firstly</b>, You have to put your team information (No of Students, Shift and Choice of Project/Internship). <b>Secondly</b>, you have to provide all the members Student ID, Name, DIU Email Address and Phone Number. <b>Thirdly</b>, you have to provide a tentative title and your area of interest. The \"Tentative Title\" should be understandable with the \"Area of Interest\". If you do not find your area in the list choose \"Others\" option and name the area. <b>Finally</b>, you have to provide three choices of your preferred Supervisor. <b>It is not guaranteed that your first choice of supervisor will be assigned.</b> Assigning supervisor is subject to the rules and regulations set by the project/internship committee.</string>

    <string name="stepping_to_the_registration">Stepping to the registration</string>
    <string name="details_stepping_to_the_registration"><b>First Step:</b>\n\u25CF Choose No of Students in your team. According to the rules, maximum 3 member teams are allowed. (If you want to make a team having 4 members you have to proceed with a \"Formal Application to the Head of The Department\" and have to fill up a different form which is available in CSE department. If you have an approved application (approved by Head of the Department), then you do not have to submit this registration.\n\u25CF Choose your shift (Day or Evening). Day shift Students cannot merge a team with Evening Shift students and vice versa. Choose your choice (Project or Internship).\n\u25CF Choosing \"Project\" will include development project and research project both. \n\n<b>Second Step:</b> Provide your team members Student ID, Name, DIU Email Address and Phone Number. All the fields are mandatory to be filled. \n\n<b>Third Step:</b> Provide a Tentative Title and Area of Interest. You can change your tentative title after assigning a supervisor consulting with him/her, But you cannot change your area of interest after assigning a supervisor to your team. \n\n<b>Fourth Step:</b> Provide Three (3) supervisors name and Initial. Select your preferred supervisor initial from the drop-down list. Choices are based on your priority.</string>

    <string name="cautions">CAUTIONS</string>
    <string name="details_cautions">\u25CF <b>Only one member from each team should fill up this form. Multiple submission are strictly not encouraged.</b> \n\u25CF <b>It is not guaranteed that your first choice of supervisor will be assigned. Project/Internship Committee will assign a supervisor according to the rules and regulations advised by the honorable head of the department.</b> \n\u25CF <b>After assigning a supervisor, you cannot change your supervisor before Title Defense. Changing supervisor is not appreciated at all.</b></string>

    <string name="number_of_students">Number of students? <font color='red'>*</font></string>
    <string name="day_evening">Day/Evening? <font color='red'>*</font></string>
    <string name="project_internship">Project/Internship? <font color='red'>*</font></string>
    <string name="internship_is_applicable_for_evening_student_only_if_any">Internship is applicable for Evening student only (if any).</string>
    <string name="student_id_name_email_and_cell_no">Student ID, Name, Email and Cell No. <font color='red'>*</font></string>
    <string name="write_the_student_id_name_email_and_cell_according_to_your_group">Write the student ID, Name, Email and Cell according to your group</string>

    <string name="internship">Internship</string>
    <string name="project">Project</string>
    <string name="project_internship_title">Project/Internship Title <font color='red'>*</font></string>
    <string name="project_internship_type">Project/Internship Type <font color='red'>*</font></string>
    <string name="area_of_interest">Area of Interest <font color='red'>*</font></string>
    <string name="choose_a_see_the_topic_and_supervisor_section">Choose a topic. For details information about these topics, see the Topic and Supervisor section.</string>
    <string name="supervisor_choices">Supervisor Choices <font color='red'>*</font></string>
    <string name="i_we_do_hereby_agree_that_assigning_supervisor_according_to_the_choice_is_not_guaranteed">I/We do hereby agree that, assigning supervisor according to the choice is not guaranteed always.<font color='red'>*</font></string>

    <string name="write_the_three_different_initial_of_the_supervisors_according_to_your_choice_only_initial_do_not_write_full_name_note_it_is_not_confirmed_that_you_will_get_the_supervisor_if_you_give_his_her_initial_in_all_three_choice">Write the three different initial of the supervisors according to your choice! <b>Only Initial with Capital letter, do not write full name.</b> Note: It is not confirmed that you will get the supervisor if you give his/her initial in all three choice.</string>
    <string name="check_your_internet_connection_and_pull_to_refresh">Check your internet connection\nand pull to refresh</string>

    <string-array name="area_of_interests">
        <item>Mobile Application (Traditional)</item>
        <item>Mobile Application (Game Development)</item>
        <item>Web Application</item>
        <item>Data Mining</item>
        <item>Machine Learning</item>
        <item>Internet of Things (IoT)</item>
        <item>Networking</item>
        <item>Cloud Computing</item>
        <item>Image Processing/Computer Vision</item>
        <item>Bioinformatics</item>
        <item>Human Computer Interaction</item>
        <item>Robotics</item>
        <item>Embedded System</item>
        <item>Other</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="supervisors">
        <item>abdus.cse@diu.edu.bd</item>
        <item>akterhossain@daffodilvarsity.edu.bd</item>
        <item>saiful.cse@diu.edu.bd</item>
        <item>bonny.cse@diu.edu.bd</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="project_internship_type">
        <item>Choose a type</item>
        <item>Development Project</item>
        <item>Research Project</item>
        <item>Internship</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="user_role_to_login">
        <item>Choose a role to login</item>
        <item>Student</item>
        <item>Supervisor</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="sign_up">Sign Up</string>
    <string name="login">Login</string>

    <string name="one_stop_instructions">ONE STOP INSTRUCTIONS</string>
    <string name="in_the_department_of_computer_science_and_engineering_cse_of_daffodil_international_university_diu_final_year_students_are_involved_in_development_projects_research_projects_or_internship_works_there_is_no_bindings_for_students_so_far_in_choosing_any_of_the_above_mentioned_area_to_complete_the_six_credit_requirements_for_day_shift_students_projects_or_internship_will_continue_starting_from_l3_t3_and_end_after_completion_of_l4_t4_without_exceptions_for_evening_">In the Department of Computer Science and Engineering (CSE) of Daffodil International University (DIU), final year students are involved in development projects, research projects or internship works. There is no bindings for students so far in choosing any of the above mentioned area to complete the six credit requirements.For Day shift students, projects or internship will continue starting from L3-T3 and end after completion of L4-T4, without exceptions. For Evening shift students, projects or internship will continue starting from 7th Semester and end after completion of 9th Semester, without exceptions.\n\nTherefore, if you are a L3-T2 (Day) or 6th Semester (Evening) student, start planning for your project ideas, team members and so on.</string>

    <string name="one_life_one_project_one_supervisor">One Life!!! One Project!!! One Supervisor!!!</string>
    <string name="for_your_final_year_project_or_internship_you_have_to_work_under_kind_supervision_of_any_of_the_permanent_faculty_members_of_cse_department_on_condition_you_can_work_under_some_of_our_adjunct_professor_or_part_time_faculty_members_one_supervisor_and_one_co_supervisor_will_be_assigned_to_each_project_team_for_finding_present_supervisor_s_list_click_here_for_finding_general_questions_about_supervisor_who_could_be_my_supervisor_while_doing_the_registration_for_title_defense_in_l3_t3_you_have_to_provide_three_choices_for_your_supervisor_upon_your_project_area_chosen_and_expected_supervisors_criteria_project_internship_committee_will_assign_a_supervisor_and_a_co_supervisor">For your final year project or internship, you have to work under kind supervision of any of the permanent faculty members of CSE Department. On condition, you can work under some of our Adjunct Professor or Part-time faculty members. One supervisor and one co-supervisor will be assigned to each project team. For finding topic and supervisor list please check <b>topics and supervisors</b> section.\n\nWhile doing the registration for Title Defense in L3-T3, you have to provide three choices for your supervisor. Upon your project area chosen and expected supervisors criteria, project/internship committee will assign a supervisor and a co-supervisor.</string>

    <string name="team_formations">Team Formations</string>
    <string name="one_specific_project_could_be_done_by_only_one_team_project_internship_committee_will_ensure_that_all_the_projects_presented_in_the_title_defense_are_unique_for_choosing_a_project_try_to_take_a_recent_topic_like_real_life_problem_domain_and_its_probable_computerized_solution_for_research_project_try_to_cover_the_recent_research_areas_and_state_of_the_art_condition_on_that_area_a_novel_methodology_or_improvement_in_existing_methodologies_would_be_a_better_contribution_of_your_research_for_internship_you_have_to_choose_a_it_company_and_have_to_work_on_some_projects_of_that_company_your_internship_goal_will_be_to_earn_practical_experience_by_working_in_professional_environment_for_development_or_research_project_no_of_team_member_1_to_3_four_members_could_be_allowed_by_a_formal_application_to_the_head_of_the_department_team_members_could_be_from_different_sections_but_only_one_registration_is_enough_for_forming_the_team_no_need_to_re_registration_from_each_section_for_internship_internships_are_considered_to_be_individual_work_internship_teams_will_be_one_man_army">One specific project could be done by only one team. Project/Internship committee will ensure that all the projects presented in the Title Defense are unique. For research project, try to cover the recent research areas and state-of-the-art condition on that area.For internship, you have to choose a IT company and have to work on some projects of that company.\n\nFor Development or Research Project:\n\u25CF No of Team member: <b>1 to 3</b>. Four members could be allowed by a formal application to the Head of the Department. Team members could be from different sections. \n\nFor Internship:\n\u25CF Internships are considered to be <b>individual</b> work. Internship teams will be one man army.</string>

    <string name="pre_phase_i">Pre-phase I</string>
    <string name="as_mentioned_above_the_main_task_as_a_final_year_student_is_to_do_registration_properly_and_attend_the_title_defense_for_day_shift_students_l3_t3_they_have_to_attend_the_title_defense_in_pre_phase_i_for_evening_shift_students_7th_semester_they_have_to_attend_the_title_defense_on_their_pre_phase_as_they_have_only_one_semester_for_pre_phase_steps_to_attend_the_title_defense_complete_title_defense_registration_online_a_supervisor_and_a_co_supervisor_will_be_assigned_by_the_project_internship_committee_contact_with_your_supervisor_and_consult_about_your_project_idea_and_preparation_of_title_defense_attend_the_title_defense_get_the_result_of_title_defense_from_your_supervisor_for_each_above_mentioned_steps_you_will_get_formal_emails_from_project_internship_committee_if_you_are_not_getting_any_email_check_if_your_email_is_properly_added_in_the_studentcse_diu_edu_bd_contact_cse_office_for_further_query_regarding_email_issues_after_successful_completion_of_title_defense_in_pre_phase_i_you_have_to_attend_another_follow_up_presentation_in_front_of_your_supervisor_after_title_defense_all_the_follow_ups_until_the_phase_ii_will_be_managed_and_instructed_by_supervisors">As mentioned above the main task as a final year student is to do registration properly and attend the title defense. For day-shift students (L3-T3), they have to attend the title defense in pre-phase I. For evening-shift students (7th Semester), they have to attend the title defense on their pre-phase as they have only one semester for pre-phase.\n\nSteps to attend the Title Defense\n\u25CF <b>Complete Title Defense Registration Online.</b>\n\u25CF <b>A supervisor and a co-supervisor will be assigned by the project/internship committee</b>
        \n\u25CF <b>Contact with your supervisor and consult about your project idea and preparation of title defense</b>\n\u25CF <b>Attend the Title Defense</b>\n\u25CF <b>Get the result of Title Defense from your supervisor.</b>\n\nFor each above mentioned steps, you will get formal emails from project/internship committee. If you are not getting any email, check if your email is properly added in the <b>studentcse@diu.edu.bd</b>. Contact CSE office for further query regarding email issues.</string>

    <string name="title_defense">Title Defense</string>
    <string name="your_final_year_project_or_internship_starts_with_the_mandatory_title_defense_title_defense_is_the_defense_where_each_team_have_to_present_their_project_idea_title_defense_presentation_focuses_on_project_internship_title_project_type_development_research_or_internship_motivation_of_the_project_objectives_of_the_project_and_expected_outcome_from_this_proposed_project_for_title_defense_presentation_you_have_to_create_a_google_site_for_your_team_the_google_site_must_have_the_above_mentioned_topics_including_your_team_information_team_name_members_name_id_and_supervisor_co_supervisors_information_name_and_designation">Your final year project or internship starts with the mandatory Title Defense. Title defense is the defense where each team have to present their project idea. \n\nTitle Defense Presentation focuses on: <b>\n\u25CF Project/Internship Title, \n\u25CF Project Type (Development, Research or Internship), \n\u25CF Motivation of the project, \n\u25CF Objectives of the project and Expected Outcome from this proposed project.</b>\n\nFor Title Defense presentation, you have to create a Google Site for your team. The Google Site must have the above mentioned topics including your team information (Team Name, Members Name, ID) and Supervisor, Co-supervisors Information (Name and Designation).</string>

    <string name="pre_phase_ii">Pre-phase II</string>
    <string name="pre_phase_ii_is_only_for_day_shift_students_l4_t1_in_this_semester_you_have_to_face_two_follow_ups_one_before_midterm_and_one_before_semester_final_and_show_your_progress_in_project_all_the_follow_ups_are_managed_and_instructed_by_supervisors_contact_your_supervisor_to_know_the_date_of_follow_ups_project_internship_committee_will_circulate_notice_emails_to_each_supervisor_and_project_teams_about_the_follow_up_dates">Pre-phase II is only for day-shift students<b>(L4-T1)</b> . In this semester you have to face two follow-ups (one before midterm and one before semester final) and show your progress in project. All the follow-ups are managed and instructed by supervisors. Contact your supervisor to know the date of follow-ups. \n\nProject/internship committee will circulate notice emails to each supervisor and project teams about the follow-up dates.</string>

    <string name="phase_i">Phase I</string>
    <string name="in_phase_i_both_day_shift_l4_t2_and_evening_shift_8th_semester_students_have_to_be_involved_in_final_year_project_in_this_semester_you_have_to_complete_the_following_tasks_follow_up_1_follow_up_2_follow_ups_will_be_completed_as_instructed_by_supervisor_in_the_same_fashion_it_is_done_in_pre_phases">In phase I, <b>both day-shift (L4-T2) and evening-shift (8th Semester) students</b> have to be involved in final year project. In this semester you have to complete the following tasks. \n\n\u25CF Follow-up 1 \n\u25CF Follow-up 2 \n\nFollow-ups will be completed as instructed by supervisor in the same fashion it is done in pre-phases.</string>

    <string name="phase_ii">Phase II</string>
    <string name="in_phase_ii_both_day_shift_l4_t3_and_evening_shift_9th_semester_students_have_to_be_involved_in_final_year_project_in_this_semester_you_have_to_complete_the_following_tasks_follow_up_1_pre_defense_follow_up_1_will_be_completed_as_instructed_by_supervisor_in_the_same_fashion_it_is_done_in_previous_phases_there_will_be_no_second_follow_up_in_phase_ii_but_yo_have_to_face_the_pre_defense">In phase II,<b>both day-shift (L4-T3) and evening-shift (9th Semester) students</b> have to be involved in final year project. In this semester you have to complete the following tasks.\n\n\u25CF Follow-up 1\n\u25CF Pre-defense \n\nFollow-up 1 will be completed as instructed by supervisor in the same fashion it is done in previous phases. There will be no second follow-up in phase II, but yo have to face the pre-defense.</string>

    <string name="pre_defense">Pre-defense</string>
    <string name="pre_defense_is_considered_to_be_trail_of_final_defense_and_all_the_senior_faculty_members_are_considered_to_be_the_judge_of_pre_defense_pre_defense_presentation_is_a_pre_requisite_to_face_the_final_defense_thus_it_is_mandatory_for_pre_defense_you_have_to_complete_the_following_task_steps_of_to_attend_pre_defense_complete_all_the_follow_ups_in_previous_phases_consult_with_the_supervisor_to_send_your_team_information_to_the_project_internship_committee_within_the_deadline_get_instructions_from_project_internship_committee_through_email_attend_the_pre_defense_presentation_with_your_project_google_site_printed_report_screen_cast_videos_and_other_necessary_documents_as_instructed_in_the_email_get_the_result_of_pre_defense_from_your_supervisor">Pre-defense is considered to be trail of final defense and all the senior faculty members are considered to be the judge of pre-defense. Pre-defense presentation is a pre-requisite to face the final defense, thus it is mandatory. For pre-defense you have to complete the following task.\n\nSteps of to attend Pre-defense\n\u25CF <b>Complete all the follow-ups in previous phases.\n\u25CF Consult with the supervisor to send your team information to the project/internship committee within the deadline.\n\u25CF Get instructions from project/internship committee through email.\n\u25CF Attend the pre-defense presentation with your project Google Site, printed report, screen-cast videos and other necessary documents as instructed in the email.\n\u25CF Get the result of Pre-defense from your supervisor.</b></string>

    <string name="final_defense">Final Defense</string>
    <string name="final_defense_is_the_last_and_final_presentation_you_have_to_face_to_defend_your_final_year_project_research_or_internship_works_this_is_called_defense_as_you_have_to_defend_each_and_every_issues_requirement_analysis_project_planning_implementations_testing_validation_verification_version_control_report_writing_synchronization_between_development_work_and_report_usually_the_most_senior_faculties_are_considered_to_become_the_judge_of_final_defense_and_additionally_there_must_be_one_or_more_external_faculties_from_other_universities_steps_to_attend_the_final_defense_attend_the_pre_defense_successfully_consult_with_supervisor_and_do_modifications_as_mentioned_by_the_pre_defense_judges_get_instructions_from_project_internship_committee_through_email_attend_the_final_defense_presentation_with_your_project_google_site_printed_report_screen_cast_videos_and_other_necessary_documents_as_instructed_in_the_email_get_the_result_from_the_exam_controller_office_final_defense_is_the_last_session_for_interacting_with_the_supervisor_as_well_as_project_internship_committee">Final defense is the last and final presentation you have to face to defend your final year project, research or internship works. This is called defense as you have to defend each and every issues (requirement analysis, project planning, implementations, testing, validation, verification, version control, report writing, synchronization between development work and report).\n\nSteps to attend the Final Defense<b>\n\u25CF Attend the pre-defense successfully. \n\u25CF Consult with supervisor and do modifications as mentioned by the pre-defense judges. \n\u25CF Get instructions from project/internship committee through email.\n\u25CF Attend the Final Defense presentation with your project Google Site, printed report, screen-cast videos and other necessary documents as instructed in the email.\n\u25CF Get the result from the Exam Controller office.</b></string>

    <string name="contact_persons">CONTACT PERSONS</string>
    <string name="narayan_ranjan_chakraborty_assistant_professor_office_room_room_no_111_daffodil_tower_mobile_no_8801617379897_email_narayan_daffodilvarsity_edu_bd"><b>Narayan Ranjan Chakraborty</b> \nAssistant Professor \nOffice Room: Room No-111, Daffodil Tower \nMobile No: +8801617379897 \nEmail: narayan@daffodilvarsity.edu.bd \n\n<b>Shah Md. Tanvir Siddiquee</b>\nSenior Lecturer\nOffice Room: Room No-111, Daffodil Tower\nMobile No: +8801712560297\nEmail: tanvir.cse@diu.edu.bd\n\n<b>Ahmed Al Marouf</b>\nLecturer\nOffice Room: Room-502, 5th Floor, CSE Building\nMobile No: +8801911784448\nEmail: marouf.cse@diu.edu.bd\n\n<b>Anup Majumder</b>\nLecturer\nOffice Room: Room-512, 5th Floor, CSE Building\nMobile No: +8801725228874\nEmail: anup.cse@diu.edu.bd</string>

    <string name="semester_wise_project_timeline">Semester-wise Project Timeline</string>
    <string name="u25cf_for_day_shift_students">● For Day Shift Students:</string>
    <string name="for_evening_shift_students">● For Evening Shift Students</string>
    <string name="level_term">Did you completed <b>L3-T2</b> (8 semester) for day shift students or <b>L2-T3</b> (6 semester) for evening shift students?</string>

</resources>
